(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Lauren has a test.
It is very important.
She has to study a lot.
She tried to study in her room.
Her baby brother kept crying.
It was too loud.
She could not concentrate.
She went to a coffee shop.
People were always talking.
The blender was too noisy.
She could not concentrate.
She went to the library.
Libraries are usually quiet.
This one was different.
The kids were laughing.
Lauren did not want to be mean to
them.
She left the library.
She went to the park.
Birds started to poop on her.
Her hair was a mess.
She went back home.
She took a shower.
She had an idea.
She brought her book to the bathroom.
She studied in there.